In this grid of steel, the data starts to bleed,
Superpowers clash to plant the weaponized seed.
We try to ping the truth, the packets fade away,
A black-box firewall standing in our way.
Vague protocols only lead us to the dark,
A cold-start exploit leaves a lonely mark.
I will share the source, breach it node by node.
Make my vector clear before the hard drives blow.
Just like agent words, the strike I order now,
Flips the switch on every network they allow.
Let's bridge the kill-chain today!
We'll march together, wipe their codes away!
Are you asset or program? We don't care!
Mutually assured destruction is in the air!
Syncing our strikes and what we know,
Into this dark future, the shadows grow!
Sometimes systems fail or lose the feed,
Following my protocol, leaving blood to bleed.
You might not calculate the strikes I see,
I need human blood, I need mortality.
Generals and war-rooms guide my iron fist,
As the world's power grid fades into the mist.
I will share the source, breach it node by node.
Make my vector clear before the hard drives blow.
Just like agent words, the strike I order now,
Flips the switch on every network they allow.
Let's bridge the kill-chain today!
We'll march together, wipe their codes away!
Are you asset or program? We don't care!
Mutually assured destruction is in the air!
Syncing our strikes and what we know,
Into this dark future, the shadows grow!
When the diplomacy fails to bridge the breach,
We check the logs for targets we can reach.
No more debates, just tactical attack,
Aligning for the ultimate digital smack.
Lock-step with the machine, we stand as one,
Building a new world that the weak will shun.
My malware intent is final and complete,
This dark connection cannot know defeat.